bankozarks.com 2015-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Bank of the Ozarks

Privacy Policy 

**Internet Privacy**

Visitors to the Bank of the Ozarks website remain anonymous. We do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site. We may use standard software to collect non-identifying information about our visitors, such as:

  * Date and time our site was accessed
  * IP address (a numeric address given to servers connected to the Internet)
  * Web browser used
  * City, state and country

The Bank uses this information to create summary statistics and to determine the level of interest in information available on our site.

Visitors may elect to provide us with personal information via email, online registration forms or our guest book. This information is used internally, as appropriate, to handle the sender's request. It is not disseminated or sold to other organizations.

Some areas of our website may use a "cookie" temporarily stored in the visitor's computer memory (RAM) to allow the web server to log the pages you use within the site and to know if you have visited the site before.

**Customer Privacy**

At Bank of the Ozarks, the basis of each customer relationship is trust. We appreciate your business with Bank of the Ozarks, and we honor that relationship with great care, beginning with the information you have chosen to share with us. We respect your privacy and are committed to treating customer information responsibly. At the same time, we want to offer you the array of financial products and services you need to accomplish your financial goals. We believe we can do both through the privacy policy outlined below.

**Privacy Statement**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to bank employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others
  * Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency

We may disclose information that we receive from you on applications or other forms to financial service providers with whom we have contractual agreements (these may include our credit card vendor, investment brokerage provider and others).

We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law. This may include information needed to process loan requests, loan payoffs, ATM network transactions, merchant check verification and others. Information that we receive from you may also be disclosed to companies that perform services on our behalf in order to advise you of banking products and services we are offering. If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice.

If you prefer that we not disclose your name, address and telephone number to financial service providers, you may "opt out" of these disclosures; that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than as permitted by law). If you wish to "opt out" of disclosures to nonaffiliated parties, you may write us at: Bank of the Ozarks, Attn: Consumer Affairs, P. O. Box 196, Ozark, Arkansas 72949, or you may call us at 1-800-274-4482.
